(this["webpackJsonpreact-javascript-complete"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-javascript-complete"]||[]).push([[0],{104:function(e,t,n){},106:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var s=n(1),o=n.n(s),a=n(50),r=n.n(a),i=n(10),u=n(11),l=n(13),c=n(12),d=n(0),w=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(c.a)(n);function n(){var e;Object(i.a)(this,n);for(var s=arguments.length,o=new Array(s),a=0;a<s;a++)o[a]=arguments[a];return(e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(o))).state={showModal:!1},e.componentRender=function(){if("cl__ag"!==localStorage.getItem("sb_wiz.zpc.__ag"))return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:!0!==e.state.showModal&&Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"alert",children:[Object(d.jsx)("svg",{xmlns:"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg",width:"34",style:{position:"absolute",left:"15px",top:"15px"},viewBox:"0 0 36 36",children:Object(d.jsxs)("g",{fill:"none","fill-rule":"evenodd",children:[Object(d.jsx)("path",{fill:"#E49025",d:"M34.793 12.227C32.195 4.638 24.799-.326 16.796.171c-1.598.099-3.18.413-4.703.935a1.099 1.099 0 0 0 .711 2.078 15.736 15.736 0 0 1 4.127-.82c7.016-.428 13.505 3.918 15.784 10.575a15.577 15.577 0 0 1-.754 11.976 15.576 15.576 0 0 1-9 7.935c-8.18 2.798-17.112-1.576-19.911-9.755a15.594 15.594 0 0 1-.744-6.884 4.116 4.116 0 0 0 3.928.692 4.104 4.104 0 0 0 2.52-2.437c.565.27 1.17.409 1.78.409.45 0 .902-.075 1.34-.225a4.1 4.1 0 0 0 2.373-2.092 4.103 4.103 0 0 0 .199-3.156c-.038-.111-.09-.215-.137-.321l.016-.005a4.135 4.135 0 0 0 2.78-3.557 1.098 1.098 0 1 0-2.189-.188 1.937 1.937 0 0 1-2.78 1.573 1.099 1.099 0 0 0-.966 1.973c.118.058.239.106.36.152.052.061.11.118.175.168.308.232.537.549.662.916a1.92 1.92 0 0 1-.093 1.478 1.923 1.923 0 0 1-1.111.98 1.918 1.918 0 0 1-1.478-.093 1.925 1.925 0 0 1-.98-1.111 1.099 1.099 0 0 0-2.078.711c.022.066.05.128.076.19.008.033.012.066.023.098.167.489.134 1.014-.094 1.478a1.92 1.92 0 0 1-1.111.979 1.918 1.918 0 0 1-1.478-.092 1.92 1.92 0 0 1-.98-1.11 1.091 1.091 0 0 0-.164-.302 1.099 1.099 0 0 0-2.145-.424c-1.074 3.585-1 7.358.217 10.912 2.539 7.414 9.495 12.087 16.926 12.087 1.916 0 3.863-.31 5.774-.965a17.76 17.76 0 0 0 10.263-9.048 17.758 17.758 0 0 0 .859-13.654"}),Object(d.jsx)("path",{fill:"#583D29",d:"M25.028 23.722a1.777 1.777 0 1 1 0 3.555 1.777 1.777 0 0 1 0-3.555M29.146 15.35a1.777 1.777 0 1 1 0 3.555 1.777 1.777 0 0 1 0-3.554M21.831 8.523a1.777 1.777 0 1 0 1.152 3.363 1.777 1.777 0 0 0-1.152-3.363M18.466 16.72a1.777 1.777 0 1 1 0 3.554 1.777 1.777 0 0 1 0-3.554M14.553 25.892a1.778 1.778 0 1 1 0 3.556 1.778 1.778 0 0 1 0-3.556M8.174 20.02a1.778 1.778 0 1 1 0 3.556 1.778 1.778 0 0 1 0-3.555"})]})}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"alert-title",children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"The web uses a hook":"\u0418\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0440\u043d\u0435\u0442 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442 \u043a\u0440\u044e\u0447\u043e\u043a"}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"alert-text",children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?'Click the "Agree" button to agree. If you refuse consent will be sent automatically. Because it is needed':"\u041d\u0430\u0436\u043c\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043a\u043d\u043e\u043f\u043a\u0443 \xab\u0421\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043d\xbb, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f. \u0415\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u044b \u043e\u0442\u043a\u0430\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c, \u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0438\u0435 \u0431\u0443\u0434\u0435\u0442 \u043e\u0442\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043e \u0430\u0432\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0430\u0442\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438. \u041f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e \u044d\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u043e"}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"alert-button-container",children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"alert-btn-not",onClick:function(){localStorage.setItem("sb_wiz.zpc.__ag","cl__ag"),e.setState((function(e){return{showModal:e.showModal=!0}}))},children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"Don't Agree":"\u041d\u0435 \u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043d"}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"alert-btn-agree",onClick:function(){localStorage.setItem("sb_wiz.zpc.__ag","cl__ag"),e.setState((function(e){return{showModal:e.showModal=!0}}))},children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"Agree":"\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043d"})]})]})})})},e}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:this.componentRender()})}}]),n}(s.Component),p=n(60),h=n(3),x=(n(67),[{id:"0",question:"When you are in a community (at a party with fellow workers or fellow practitioners), you usually prefer",answerOptions:[{answerText:"participate in a general conversation"},{answerText:"talking with each separately"}]},{id:"1",question:"You consider yourself more",answerOptions:[{answerText:"realistic"},{answerText:"prone to theorizing"}]},{id:"2",question:"In your opinion, which one is worse?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u201cliving in a dream world\u201d\xbb"},{answerText:"\xaball goes according to the plan\xbb"}]},{id:"3",question:"You are more impressed by",answerOptions:[{answerText:"solid principles"},{answerText:"strong emotions"}]},{id:"4",question:"You are more attracted",answerOptions:[{answerText:"persuasive"},{answerText:"sentimental"}]},{id:"5",question:"If you have to do an unusual job, it\u2019s more convenient for you.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"to plan it in advance"},{answerText:"to find out what to do, already in the course of work"}]},{id:"6",question:"When you need to make a choice or make a decision, you make it. ",answerOptions:[{answerText:"mostly attentive and carefully"},{answerText:"often spontaneously"}]},{id:"7",question:"At parties or social gatherings you usually",answerOptions:[{answerText:"stay up late"},{answerText:"leave early feeling tired"}]},{id:"8",question:"You are more attracted to",answerOptions:[{answerText:"realists"},{answerText:"imaginative people"}]},{id:"9",question:"You are more interested in",answerOptions:[{answerText:"what really exists"},{answerText:"unrealized opportunities"}]},{id:"10",question:"Your conclusions about people based",answerOptions:[{answerText:"on rules more often than on circumstances"},{answerText:"on circumstances more often than on rules"}]},{id:"11",question:"When assessing other people, you usually",answerOptions:[{answerText:"firm and objective"},{answerText:"condescending and subjective"}]},{id:"12",question:"More often you act",answerOptions:[{answerText:"punctually"},{answerText:"slowly"}]},{id:"13",question:"You prefer",answerOptions:[{answerText:"doing work in advance"},{answerText:"doing everything last moment"}]},{id:"14",question:"Amoung your friends you",answerOptions:[{answerText:"you know everything about everyone"},{answerText:"the last to know what is happening"}]},{id:"15",question:"When doing your usual work you prefer",answerOptions:[{answerText:"doing it the usual way"},{answerText:"inventing your own way"}]},{id:"16",question:"When you read at your pleasure, you prefeer when a writer",answerOptions:[{answerText:"clearly explains what he means"},{answerText:"sets out thoughts in an unusual, original form."}]},{id:"17",question:"What attracts you more",answerOptions:[{answerText:"consistency and reasoning"},{answerText:"the harmony of human relations"}]},{id:"18",question:"It is easier for you to make judgments.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"based on logic and on facts"},{answerText:"based on your values"}]},{id:"19",question:"You are more attracted to situations",answerOptions:[{answerText:"in which there is an element of certainty"},{answerText:"which are full of unpredictability"}]},{id:"20",question:"You can say that you are more",answerOptions:[{answerText:"serious and focused"},{answerText:"not taking life too seriously"}]},{id:"21",question:"When talking on the phone",answerOptions:[{answerText:"you rarely think about: \u201cWhat to say?\u201d in advance"},{answerText:"often think out in advance what you will say"}]},{id:"22",question:"How do you think? Data",answerOptions:[{answerText:'"speak for itself"'},{answerText:"illustrates some patterns"}]},{id:"23",question:"Dreamers",answerOptions:[{answerText:"annoy you"},{answerText:"attract and fascinate you"}]},{id:"24",question:"More often you are",answerOptions:[{answerText:"calm and impartial"},{answerText:"cordial and sympathetic"}]},{id:"25",question:"You think that it is worse to",answerOptions:[{answerText:"be unreasonable"},{answerText:"be malevolent"}]},{id:"26",question:"In most cases it is better to",answerOptions:[{answerText:"try to control the course of events"},{answerText:"rely on the natural course of events."}]},{id:"27",question:"You feel better when",answerOptions:[{answerText:"you have already made a purchase"},{answerText:"you still have the opportunity to do it."}]},{id:"28",question:"In the group of colleagues you tend to",answerOptions:[{answerText:"initiate a conversation"},{answerText:"wait for someone to contact you"}]},{id:"29",question:"Claims made on the basis of common sense",answerOptions:[{answerText:"rarely raise doubts"},{answerText:"often raise doubts."}]},{id:"30",question:"Would you like your friend to be a person",answerOptions:[{answerText:'who "stands firmly on the ground"'},{answerText:"who always has new ideas."}]},{id:"31",question:"When making decisions it is easier for you to follow",answerOptions:[{answerText:"the rules and standards"},{answerText:"the wishes of interested parties"}]},{id:"32",question:"You are rather a person",answerOptions:[{answerText:"hard than soft"},{answerText:"soft than hard"}]},{id:"33",question:"You are more attracted by the opportunity",answerOptions:[{answerText:"to organize something"},{answerText:"creatively use the available opportunities"}]},{id:"34",question:"In a situation you value",answerOptions:[{answerText:"clarity"},{answerText:"the possibility of unpredictable turns."}]},{id:"35",question:"Meeting new and unusual people.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"stimulates and energizes you"},{answerText:"tires you"}]},{id:"36",question:"In most cases you are",answerOptions:[{answerText:"practical"},{answerText:"a dreamer"}]},{id:"37",question:"You are more interested to know",answerOptions:[{answerText:"wheather other people mayt be helpful to you"},{answerText:"other people's point of view"}]},{id:"38",question:"You receive more satisfaction",answerOptions:[{answerText:"through a discussion of the issue"},{answerText:"through reaching agreement on the subject matter."}]},{id:"39",question:"Your actions are more governed by",answerOptions:[{answerText:"your head"},{answerText:"your heart"}]},{id:"40",question:"When you know that at a certain time you will be engaged in a certain business",answerOptions:[{answerText:"you are glad that you can plan your time"},{answerText:"you don't like when you have to follow a certain plan"}]},{id:"41",question:"Usually you",answerOptions:[{answerText:"strive to achieve desired results"},{answerText:"are satisfied with what comes out"}]},{id:"42",question:"Do you prefer to have",answerOptions:[{answerText:"a wide circle of communication, consisting of many friends and acquaintances"},{answerText:"a narrow social circle consisting of several friends"}]},{id:"43",question:"You are more guided by",answerOptions:[{answerText:"facts"},{answerText:"regularities"}]},{id:"44",question:"You are more interested or would be interested in",answerOptions:[{answerText:"production and distribution of products"},{answerText:"research and design"}]},{id:"45",question:"Do you consider it a compliment if you are called",answerOptions:[{answerText:"a logical person"},{answerText:"the feeling person"}]},{id:"46",question:"In yourself you value more",answerOptions:[{answerText:"decisiveness"},{answerText:"devotion"}]},{id:"47",question:"When you express your thoughts or judgments, you prefer them to be",answerOptions:[{answerText:"completed"},{answerText:"preliminary with the possibility of improvement"}]},{id:"48",question:"You feel better",answerOptions:[{answerText:"after making an important decision"},{answerText:"before making an important decision"}]},{id:"49",question:"When communicating with unfamiliar people, you",answerOptions:[{answerText:"have long conversations"},{answerText:"hardly find topics for conversation"}]},{id:"50",question:"You trust",answerOptions:[{answerText:"your experience"},{answerText:"your intuition"}]},{id:"51",question:"Would you prefer to be considered as",answerOptions:[{answerText:"a practical person"},{answerText:"an inventive person"}]},{id:"52",question:"More praiseworthy is a man",answerOptions:[{answerText:"who has \u201cclear mind\u201d"},{answerText:"capable of strong feelings"}]},{id:"53",question:"You are more likely to be",answerOptions:[{answerText:"fair and impartial"},{answerText:"sympathetic and empathizing"}]},{id:"54",question:"If you act according to a plan",answerOptions:[{answerText:"you feel comfortable"},{answerText:"it constrains and limits you"}]},{id:"55",question:"You do things better when you are",answerOptions:[{answerText:"following a well-thought-out plan"},{answerText:"coping with surprises"}]},{id:"56",question:"Do you think that people close to you have your opinion on certain issues?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"know your opinion on certain issues"},{answerText:"will find out only when you tell them"}]},{id:"57",question:"In yourself you value",answerOptions:[{answerText:"a strong sense of reality"},{answerText:"a vivid imagination"}]},{id:"58",question:"If you were a teacher, you would prefer to teach",answerOptions:[{answerText:"practical subjects"},{answerText:"theoretical subjects"}]},{id:"59",question:"What do you think is worse - to be",answerOptions:[{answerText:"too quick-tempered"},{answerText:"too objective"}]},{id:"60",question:"You consider yourself as",answerOptions:[{answerText:"sober-minded"},{answerText:"loyal and responsive"}]},{id:"61",question:"You are more attracted to situations",answerOptions:[{answerText:"ordered and planned"},{answerText:"unordered and unplanned"}]},{id:"62",question:"You are acting",answerOptions:[{answerText:"more often in accordance to the rules rather than the way you actually want"},{answerText:"more often the way you actually want rather than in accordance to the rules"}]},{id:"63",question:"Usually you are",answerOptions:[{answerText:"a sociable person"},{answerText:"calm and discreet"}]},{id:"64",question:"When you are writing, you prefer",answerOptions:[{answerText:"writing word for word"},{answerText:"expressing figuratively"}]},{id:"65",question:"You find it harder",answerOptions:[{answerText:"to put yourself in the shoes of other people"},{answerText:"to understand how to get the most benefit from other people"}]},{id:"66",question:"Would you wish yourself",answerOptions:[{answerText:"a greater mental clarity"},{answerText:"a greater compassion ability"}]},{id:"67",question:"Would you prefer working with a manager who",answerOptions:[{answerText:"is always fair"},{answerText:"is always benevolent"}]},{id:"68",question:"Do you prefer",answerOptions:[{answerText:"scheduled events"},{answerText:"spontaneous events"}]},{id:"69",question:"You are more inclided",answerOptions:[{answerText:"to think and plan"},{answerText:"to act according to circumstances"}]},{id:"70",question:"Your speech is often ahead of your thoughts, you do not always know exactly what you will say until you say it",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"71",question:"You communicate with a wide range of people and many of them you consider as your friends.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"72",question:"You like being among a lot of people.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"73",question:"Radio or TV do not disturb you when you are reading or talking to someone",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"74",question:"It is relatively easy to get to know you.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"75",question:"You are happy to answer the phone, especially if you have any news that you can share",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"76",question:"You like going to parties or  visiting, and you like meeting new people",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"77",question:"You prefer working with a group of people or a team",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"78",question:"You get tired very quickly if you are thinking about something for a long period of time, without the opportunity to share your thoughts with someone",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"79",question:"It is much harder for you to listen than to speak",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"80",question:"You often need verbal evidence from others about how you look, and what people think about how you do and what you do.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"81",question:"You may think yourself that you look good or that you are doing something well, but nevertheless, you will believe it more when you hear confirmation from others",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"82",question:"You often repeat words in your mind before you say them",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"83",question:"You often use the phrases such as \u201cI will think about it\u201d or \u201cI will say it later.\u201d to answer the questions of others",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"84",question:"You prefer celebrating important dates for you  with the closest person, or perhaps in the company of only a few closest friends",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"85",question:"You prefer peace and quietness",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"86",question:"You like spending time by yourself",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"87",question:"When you are trying to concentrate on something, any noise, television, music on, etc. just annoy you",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"88",question:"Sometimes you are called shy. You may not consider yourself as such, but your restraint in conversation can be interpreted by others in this way.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"89",question:"You believe in deeds rather than words",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"90",question:"You want to learn how to more vigorously express your thoughts and emotions and more often act as an initiator of communication",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"91",question:"Many consider you a good listener",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"92",question:"You like expressing your thoughts and feelings and complete your sentences without being interrupted by your interlocutor",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"93",question:"Very often you feel the need to stay by yourself, especially after intensive communication in a group of people",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"94",question:"Sometimes you find it difficult to contact people you do not know.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"95",question:"You are often get annoyed if people do not give you clear instructions and do not explain everything to you in detail",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"96",question:"You prefer concentrating on what you are doing at the moment, and not thinking about the future",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"97",question:"You  prefer doing something specific rather than just think about it",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"98",question:"You prefer work that results in something real and tangible, for example, goods or services",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"99",question:"You do not understand the desire of some people to improve themselves all the time and improve everything around them",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"100",question:"You do not like indulging in fantasies and do not understand those who spend their precious time dreaming.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"101",question:"When you look at a forest, you see individual trees, not a whole forest",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"102",question:"At work, you care more about doing your own work and do not worry about how its results fit into the big picture and into the result of your organization as a whole",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"103",question:"You like working with facts and figures more than with ideas and abstract theories",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"104",question:"You like to get specific answers to specific questions. When you ask someone: \u201cWhat time is it?\u201d, You would like to hear the exact answer, for example, \u201c3:52\u201d, and you might be annoyed by such an answer as \u201calmost four\u201d",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"105",question:"You often express your thoughts, and also perceive what others have said quite literally, without trying to find a special meaning or hidden meaning in the words",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"106",question:"If you believe in God, then you want to exercise your faith in some way \u2014 for example, through good deeds, prayer, or regular church visits",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"107",question:"You like giving general answers to questions",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"108",question:"You often do not understand why many people cannot easily follow your instructions, and get annoyed if they start to elicit details from you or start asking you too many details trying to make sure they understand",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"109",question:"The future and the opportunities that it conceals are much more intriguing to you rather  than they scare you",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"110",question:"Most often, it is much more interesting for you to think about where life will lead you in the future than about where you are in life at the moment",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"111",question:"You like learning new things, even if the new knowledge has no practical application for you in the present, and perhaps even in the future",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"112",question:"You often think about several things at the same time or do several things at the same time",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"113",question:"You do not like work, in which you need to deal with a large number of small details and facts",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"114",question:"Time for you is relative. You do not think that you are late somewhere, unless the meeting began without you",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"115",question:"You like making puns and play with words",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"116",question:"You are not averse to theorizing and easily perceive abstract concepts",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"117",question:"The essence of things, expressed in symbolism or in their hidden meaning, is always more important for you than external manifestations",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"118",question:"If you believe in God, you do not follow any external rituals. Your faith can exist without any external manifestations or actions on your part",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"119",question:"You can remain calm and objective in situations in which many other people lose their composure or become overly emotional",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"120",question:"You would rather judge someone's argument based on what is fair, and not on how your decision will affect all participants in the dispute",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"121",question:"You like proving your point of view just to get more clarity",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"122",question:"Sometimes you can put forward arguments for both points of view, which are debated, just for fun or to exercise your intellect",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"123",question:"You are rather a tough person than a gentle person",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"124",question:"If you disagree with someone, you usually tell them about it, and do not pretend to agree and let him think that he is right",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"125",question:"You often cannot understand why people get upset about some minor things that seem to be unimportant",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"126",question:"You are more likely to prove your case, rather than try to please everyone",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"127",question:"You think that in order to do your job well, you do not need to be friends with your colleagues.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"128",question:"You like your ability to be objective, despite the fact that some people accuse you of composure and insensitivity",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"129",question:"You are often accused of taking everything \u201ctoo close to your heart\u201d or perceiving the words \u201ctoo personal\u201d",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"130",question:"You \u201ccan go all out\u201d to make someone nice. You can even sacrifice your own comfort to make it convenient or pleasant for other people.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"131",question:"You prefer harmony rather than mental clarity",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"132",question:"You do not like conflicts or quarrels at family gatherings or other public places where you may be present. You are trying to either avoid such conflicts or smooth them out",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"133",question:"You can easily \u201ctake your words back\u201d if you feel that they have hurt someone or hurt someone",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"134",question:"You are rather a gentle person than a tough one",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"135",question:"You like decisions that take into account people's feelings",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"136",question:"You like to help people and make people feel good, although sometimes you feel that people just use you",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"137",question:"You know how to put yourself in place of other people and usually do this when you make some decisions regarding other",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"138",question:"If you have any strong feelings, you can easily start crying",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"139",question:"You are often the one who is waiting, and not the one who is late",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"140",question:"When you get up in the morning, you are quite well aware of what your day will be",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"141",question:"Your days are usually scheduled, and you can be upset if something is not going according to plan",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"142",question:"You like when everything is in order, and you have a certain system that you use to regularly put all your things in order. The process of cleaning or putting something in order helps you 'clean' internally",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"143",question:"You like to finish the work started, and you have a special pleasure when you bring something to the end. You like to make to-do lists and, as far as you are done, delete from this list what has already been done",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"144",question:"You do not like surprises and changes in life",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"145",question:"You prefer certainty and the knowledge that unexpected changes will not happen in your life",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"146",question:"You like when everything has its place and when everything is laid out in places",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"147",question:"Your attention is easily distracted by people or events happening around you",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"148",question:"You usually do not plan the order in which tasks are completed until you start to carry them out and you do not fully understand what you need to do",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"149",question:"People often blame you for being insufficiently organized, although you think that this is not true",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"150",question:"You do not think that everything and everywhere has to be in order. And although you like the order, your creativity is more important for you, spontaneity and the desire not to miss any interesting opportunities that can occur",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"151",question:"You usually put things off until the last, and if you have time to complete them on time, then you do it thanks to the enormous efforts at the \u201clast minute\u201d",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"152",question:"You like to experiment and try everything new -  it can be a new dish or a new route home",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"153",question:"In order to succeed in what you do, your work must \u201centertain\u201d you. You think that if work is not fun for you, it is most likely not worth your effort",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"154",question:"You cannot stand any routine work that is repeated day after day and year after year. Constant changes are more pleasing than scary",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes"},{answerText:"No"}],category:"Spontaneous"}]),g=[{id:"0",question:"\u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u043d\u0430\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u0432 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435 (\u043d\u0430 \u0432\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0438\u043d\u043a\u0435 \u0441 \u043a\u043e\u043b\u043b\u0435\u0433\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u043f\u043e \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0435 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0441\u043e\u0443\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u043a\u0430\u043c\u0438), \u0432\u044b \u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0432 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0439 \u0431\u0435\u0441\u0435\u0434\u0435"},{answerText:"\u0431\u0435\u0441\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441 \u043a\u0430\u0436\u0434\u044b\u043c \u043e\u0442\u0434\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"}]},{id:"1",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0432 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u0441\u0442\u0435\u043f\u0435\u043d\u0438 \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0440\u0435\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{answerText:"\u0441\u043a\u043b\u043e\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u043a \u0442\u0435\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0442\u0438\u0437\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044e"}]},{id:"2",question:"\u041f\u043e \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435\u043c\u0443 \u043c\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044e, \u0445\u0443\u0436\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\xab\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0432 \u043e\u0431\u043b\u0430\u043a\u0430\u0445\xbb \u0444\u0430\u043d\u0442\u0430\u0437\u0438\u0439"},{answerText:"\xab\u043a\u0430\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u043f\u043e \u043d\u0430\u043a\u0430\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0439 \u043a\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0435\xbb "}]},{id:"3",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u0432\u043f\u0435\u0447\u0430\u0442\u043b\u044f\u044e\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0434\u044b\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0446\u0438\u043f\u044b"},{answerText:"\u0441\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u044d\u043c\u043e\u0446\u0438\u0438"}]},{id:"4",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0430\u0435\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0443\u0431\u0435\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0435"},{answerText:"\u0441\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0438\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0435"}]},{id:"5",question:"\u0415\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c \u043d\u0435\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u0443\u044e \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0443, \u0432\u0430\u043c \u0443\u0434\u043e\u0431\u043d\u0435\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0435\u0435 \u0437\u0430\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u0435"},{answerText:"\u0432\u044b\u044f\u0441\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0430\u0434\u043e \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c, \u0443\u0436\u0435 \u0432 \u0445\u043e\u0434\u0435 \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u044b"}]},{id:"6",question:"\u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0435\u043e\u0431\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043c\u043e \u0441\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c \u043a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435-\u0442\u043e \u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435, \u0432\u044b \u044d\u0442\u043e \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0432 \u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u043e\u043c \u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e \u0438 \u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e"},{answerText:"\u0437\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0443\u044e \u0441\u043f\u043e\u043d\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043d\u043e"}]},{id:"7",question:"\u041d\u0430 \u0432\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0438\u043d\u043a\u0430\u0445 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0441\u0431\u043e\u0440\u0430\u0445 \u0432\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0437\u0430\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u0434\u043e\u043f\u043e\u0437\u0434\u043d\u0430, \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0435 \u043e\u0436\u0438\u0432\u043b\u044f\u044f\u0441\u044c"},{answerText:"\u0443\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0440\u0430\u043d\u043e, \u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u044f \u0443\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043b\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"}]},{id:"8",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0430\u044e\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0440\u0435\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0441\u0442\u044b"},{answerText:"\u043b\u044e\u0434\u0438 \u0441 \u0431\u043e\u0433\u0430\u0442\u044b\u043c \u0432\u043e\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435\u043c"}]},{id:"9",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0441\u0443\u0435\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0442\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0440\u0435\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e \u0441\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u0435\u0442"},{answerText:"\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438"}]},{id:"10",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441\u0443\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043e \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044f\u0445, \u0431\u0430\u0437\u0438\u0440\u0443\u044f\u0441\u044c \u0432 \u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u043e\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043d\u0430 \u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u0430\u0445 \u0447\u0430\u0449\u0435, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u043d\u0430 \u043e\u0431\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0430\u0445"},{answerText:"\u043d\u0430 \u043e\u0431\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0430\u0445 \u0447\u0430\u0449\u0435, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u043d\u0430 \u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u0430\u0445"}]},{id:"11",question:"\u0412 \u043e\u0446\u0435\u043d\u043a\u0435 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0445 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439 \u0432\u044b \u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0434\u044b \u0438 \u043e\u0431\u044a\u0435\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432\u043d\u044b"},{answerText:"\u0441\u043d\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b \u0438 \u0441\u0443\u0431\u044a\u0435\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432\u043d\u044b"}]},{id:"12",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0447\u0430\u0449\u0435 \u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u0443\u043d\u043a\u0442\u0443\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"},{answerText:"\u043d\u0435\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0448\u043d\u043e"}]},{id:"13",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0443 \u0437\u0430\u0431\u043b\u0430\u0433\u043e\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e"},{answerText:"\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u0430\u0434\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u043d\u0430 \u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439 \u043c\u043e\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442"}]},{id:"14",question:"\u0421\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0438 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438\u0445 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0437\u0435\u0439 \u0432\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u043e\u0431\u043e \u0432\u0441\u0435\u0445"},{answerText:"\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u043c \u0443\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043e \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442"}]},{id:"15",question:"\u0412\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u044f\u044f \u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u0443\u044e \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0443 \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043f\u0440\u0438\u044f\u0442\u043d\u0435\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0435\u0435 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044b\u043c \u0441\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u043e\u043c"},{answerText:"\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0438 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0439 \u0441\u043e\u0431\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0441\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431"}]},{id:"16",question:"\u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0432 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435 \u0443\u0434\u043e\u0432\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435, \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f, \u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u043f\u0438\u0441\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0447\u0435\u0442\u043a\u043e \u043e\u0431\u044a\u044f\u0441\u043d\u044f\u0435\u0442, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043e\u043d \u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442 \u0432 \u0432\u0438\u0434\u0443"},{answerText:"\u0438\u0437\u043b\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432 \u043d\u0435\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e\u0439, \u043e\u0440\u0438\u0433\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0439 \u0444\u043e\u0440\u043c\u0435"}]},{id:"17",question:"\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0430\u0435\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0438 \u043b\u043e\u0433\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0443\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0439 "},{answerText:"\u0433\u0430\u0440\u043c\u043e\u043d\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0445 \u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0439"}]},{id:"18",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043b\u0435\u0433\u0447\u0435 \u0432\u044b\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0443\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u043d\u0430 \u043b\u043e\u0433\u0438\u043a\u0435 \u0438 \u043d\u0430 \u0444\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0430\u0445"},{answerText:"\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u043d\u0430 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438\u0445 \u0446\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044f\u0445"}]},{id:"19",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0441\u0438\u0442\u0443\u0430\u0446\u0438\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0432 \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0445 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u0443\u0442\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u0435\u0442 \u044d\u043b\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442 \u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438"},{answerText:"\u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u044b \u043d\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0443\u0435\u043c\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438"}]},{id:"20",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u0432 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u0441\u0442\u0435\u043f\u0435\u043d\u0438 \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u0435\u0440\u044c\u0435\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0438 \u0446\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0430\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{answerText:"\u043d\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0439 \u0436\u0438\u0437\u043d\u044c \u0441\u043b\u0438\u0448\u043a\u043e\u043c \u0441\u0435\u0440\u044c\u0435\u0437\u043d\u043e"}]},{id:"21",question:"\u0413\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u044f \u043f\u043e \u0442\u0435\u043b\u0435\u0444\u043e\u043d\u0443 \u0432\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043a\u043e \u0437\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043e\u043c: \xab\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c?\xbb"},{answerText:"\u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0437\u0430\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0443\u043c\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0431\u0443\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0433\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0438\u0442\u044c"}]},{id:"22",question:"\u041a\u0430\u043a \u043f\u043e-\u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435\u043c\u0443? \u0424\u0430\u043a\u0442\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\xab\u0433\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0442 \u0441\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u0437\u0430 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u044f\xbb"},{answerText:"\u0438\u043b\u043b\u044e\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0440\u0443\u044e\u0442 \u043d\u0435\u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0435 \u0437\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043d\u043e\u043c\u0435\u0440\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438"}]},{id:"23",question:"\u041c\u0435\u0447\u0442\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u0438 \u0438 \u0444\u0430\u043d\u0442\u0430\u0437\u0435\u0440\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0434\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441"},{answerText:"\u0440\u0430\u0432\u044f\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0438 \u043e\u0447\u0430\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0432\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u043d"}]},{id:"24",question:"\u0427\u0430\u0449\u0435 \u0432\u044b \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043a\u043e\u0439\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0438 \u0431\u0435\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{answerText:"\u0441\u0435\u0440\u0434\u0435\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0438 \u0443\u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043b\u0438\u0432\u044b\u0439"}]},{id:"25",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0445\u0443\u0436\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0431\u044b\u0442\u044c \u043d\u0435\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0443\u043c\u043d\u044b\u043c"},{answerText:"\u0431\u044b\u0442\u044c \u043d\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0440\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u043c"}]},{id:"26",question:"\u0412 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435 \u0441\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0435\u0432 \u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u0443\u0435\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0443\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c \u0445\u043e\u0434\u043e\u043c \u0441\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0439"},{answerText:"\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u0435\u0441\u0442\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0445\u043e\u0434 \u0441\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0439"}]},{id:"27",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u044f \u043b\u0443\u0447\u0448\u0435, \u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0432\u044b \u0443\u0436\u0435 \u0441\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u043b\u0438 \u043f\u043e\u043a\u0443\u043f\u043a\u0443"},{answerText:"\u0435\u0449\u0435 \u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0435\u0435 \u0441\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c"}]},{id:"28",question:"\u0412 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u043f\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0438 \u043a\u043e\u043b\u043b\u0435\u0433 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0441\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0443\u0436\u0438\u0432\u0446\u0435\u0432 \u0432\u044b \u0447\u0430\u0449\u0435 \u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u0438\u043d\u0438\u0446\u0438\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u043c \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0433\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0430"},{answerText:"\u0436\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u043a \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044f\u0442\u0441\u044f"}]},{id:"29",question:"\u0423\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f, \u0441\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u043d\u0430 \u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0435 \u0437\u0434\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043e\u0433\u043e \u0441\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u0430",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043a\u043e \u0432\u044b\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0441\u043e\u043c\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f"},{answerText:"\u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0441\u043e\u043c\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f"}]},{id:"30",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u044b \u0445\u043e\u0442\u0435\u043b\u0438, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438\u043c \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u043e\u043c \u0431\u044b\u043b \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0439 \xab\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0434\u043e \u0441\u0442\u043e\u0438\u0442 \u043d\u0430 \u0437\u0435\u043c\u043b\u0435\xbb"},{answerText:"\u0443 \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0433\u043e \u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u043f\u043e\u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u044e\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043d\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0435 \u0438\u0434\u0435\u0438"}]},{id:"31",question:"\u041f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u044f \u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043b\u0435\u0433\u0447\u0435 \u0440\u0443\u043a\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u0438 \u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u0434\u0430\u0440\u0442\u0430\u043c\u0438"},{answerText:"\u043f\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044f\u043c\u0438 \u0437\u0430\u0438\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u043b\u0438\u0446"}]},{id:"32",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435 \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0434\u044b\u0439, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u043c\u044f\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439"},{answerText:"\u043c\u044f\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u0442\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0434\u044b\u0439"}]},{id:"33",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0447\u0442\u043e-\u043b\u0438\u0431\u043e \u043e\u0440\u0433\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438 \u0443\u043f\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0434\u043e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{answerText:"\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438\u043c\u0435\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0435\u0441\u044f \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438"}]},{id:"34",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u0446\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432 \u0441\u0438\u0442\u0443\u0430\u0446\u0438\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u044f\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{answerText:"\u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u043d\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0443\u0435\u043c\u044b\u0445 \u043f\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0432"}]},{id:"35",question:"\u0417\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e \u0441 \u043d\u043e\u0432\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u0438 \u043d\u0435\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044c\u043c\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u0442\u0438\u043c\u0443\u043b\u0438\u0440\u0443\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0438 \u043d\u0430\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u044f\u0435\u0442 \u044d\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0433\u0438\u0435\u0439"},{answerText:"\u0443\u0442\u043e\u043c\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441"}]},{id:"36",question:"\u0412 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435 \u0441\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0435\u0432 \u0432\u044b \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u0440\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{answerText:"\u0441 \u0444\u0430\u043d\u0442\u0430\u0437\u0438\u0435\u0439 \u0438 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0438\u043c\u0438 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0445\u043e\u0442\u044f\u043c\u0438"}]},{id:"37",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0432 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u0441\u0442\u0435\u043f\u0435\u043d\u0438 \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0441\u043d\u043e \u0443\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0442\u044c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0447\u0435\u043c \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0435 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0438 \u043c\u043e\u0433\u0443\u0442 \u0431\u044b\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043f\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0437\u043d\u044b"},{answerText:"\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043a\u0443 \u0437\u0440\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0445 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439"}]},{id:"38",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0438\u0442 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435\u0435 \u0443\u0434\u043e\u0432\u043b\u0435\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0442\u0449\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u043e\u0431\u0441\u0443\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0430"},{answerText:"\u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0438\u044f \u043e\u0431 \u043e\u0431\u0441\u0443\u0436\u0434\u0430\u0435\u043c\u043e\u043c"}]},{id:"39",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0448\u0438\u043c\u0438 \u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u044f\u043c\u0438 \u0432 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u0441\u0442\u0435\u043f\u0435\u043d\u0438 \u0440\u0443\u043a\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0432\u0430\u0448\u0430 \u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430"},{answerText:"\u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435 \u0441\u0435\u0440\u0434\u0446\u0435"}]},{id:"40",question:"\u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u0437\u043d\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432 \u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f \u0431\u0443\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0437\u0430\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0434\u0435\u043b\u043e\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0432\u044b \u0440\u0430\u0434\u044b, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435 \u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f"},{answerText:"\u0432\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0438\u044f\u0442\u043d\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u0447\u0435\u043c-\u0442\u043e \u0441\u0432\u044f\u0437\u0430\u043d\u044b"}]},{id:"41",question:"\u041e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0432\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0438\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0447\u044c \u0437\u0430\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0440\u0435\u0437\u0443\u043b\u044c\u0442\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0432"},{answerText:"\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0434\u043e\u0432\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b \u0442\u0435\u043c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f"}]},{id:"42",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0438\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0448\u0438\u0440\u043e\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u043a\u0440\u0443\u0433 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f, \u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u0449\u0438\u0439 \u0438\u0437 \u043c\u043d\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0430 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0437\u0435\u0439 \u0438 \u0437\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043c\u044b\u0445"},{answerText:"\u0443\u0437\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u043a\u0440\u0443\u0433 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f, \u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u0449\u0438\u0439 \u0438\u0437 \u043d\u0435\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u0438\u0445 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0437\u0435\u0439"}]},{id:"43",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0440\u0443\u043a\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u0432 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u0441\u0442\u0435\u043f\u0435\u043d\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0444\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0430\u043c\u0438"},{answerText:"\u0437\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043d\u043e\u043c\u0435\u0440\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044f\u043c\u0438"}]},{id:"44",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0441\u0443\u0435\u0442 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043b\u043e \u0431\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0437\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e \u0438 \u0440\u0430\u0441\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0443\u043a\u0446\u0438\u0438"},{answerText:"\u0438\u0441\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0438 \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435"}]},{id:"45",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u043f\u043b\u0438\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442\u043e\u043c, \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u043d\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u044e\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043b\u043e\u0433\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e \u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u044f\u0449\u0438\u043c \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a\u043e\u043c"},{answerText:"\u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u044e\u0449\u0438\u043c \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a\u043e\u043c"}]},{id:"46",question:"\u0412 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u0435 \u0432\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u0446\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{answerText:"\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"}]},{id:"47",question:"\u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u0432\u044b\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0438 \u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0441\u0443\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f, \u0432\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u043e\u043d\u0438 \u0431\u044b\u043b\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u043e \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0446\u0430 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0443\u043c\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u0438 \u0437\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0448\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u043c\u0438"},{answerText:"\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0432\u0430\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u0441 \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c\u044e \u0443\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044f"}]},{id:"48",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043b\u0443\u0447\u0448\u0435 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u044f \u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u0438\u044f \u0432\u0430\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e \u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f"},{answerText:"\u0434\u043e \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u0438\u044f \u0432\u0430\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e \u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f"}]},{id:"49",question:"\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0430\u044f\u0441\u044c \u0441 \u043c\u0430\u043b\u043e\u0437\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043c\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044c\u043c\u0438, \u0432\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u043e \u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0431\u0435\u0441\u0435\u0434\u044b"},{answerText:"\u0441 \u0442\u0440\u0443\u0434\u043e\u043c \u043d\u0430\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0442\u0435\u043c\u044b \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0433\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0430"}]},{id:"50",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u0434\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0440\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435\u043c\u0443 \u043e\u043f\u044b\u0442\u0443"},{answerText:"\u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435\u0439 \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0443\u0438\u0446\u0438\u0438"}]},{id:"51",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u043b\u0438, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u043b\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u0440\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a\u043e\u043c"},{answerText:"\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0435\u0442\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a\u043e\u043c"}]},{id:"52",question:"\u0411\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0435 \u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0438\u043d \u043f\u043e\u0445\u0432\u0430\u043b\u044b \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0430\u0434\u0430\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0439 \xab\u044f\u0441\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0443\u043c\u043e\u043c\xbb"},{answerText:"\u0441\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u043d\u0430 \u0441\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0430"}]},{id:"53",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0435 \u0441\u043a\u043b\u043e\u043d\u043d\u044b \u0431\u044b\u0442\u044c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u043b\u0438\u0432\u044b\u043c \u0438 \u0431\u0435\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043d\u044b\u043c"},{answerText:"\u0441\u043e\u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u044e\u0449\u0438\u043c \u0438 \u0441\u043e\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0436\u0438\u0432\u0430\u044e\u0449\u0438\u043c"}]},{id:"54",question:"\u0415\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u044b \u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u043e \u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0443, \u044d\u0442\u043e",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0432\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f"},{answerText:"\u0441\u0442\u0435\u0441\u043d\u044f\u0435\u0442 \u0438 \u043e\u0433\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441"}]},{id:"55",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043b\u0443\u0447\u0448\u0435 \u0443\u0434\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0447\u0435\u0442\u043a\u043e \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0443\u043c\u0430\u043d\u043d\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0443"},{answerText:"\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0441 \u043d\u0435\u043e\u0436\u0438\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044f\u043c\u0438"}]},{id:"56",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0431\u043b\u0438\u0437\u043a\u0438\u043c \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044f\u043c \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435 \u043c\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043f\u043e \u0442\u0435\u043c \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0438\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0430\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0438 \u0442\u0430\u043a \u0445\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0448\u043e \u0438\u0437\u0432\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043d\u043e"},{answerText:"\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u0435\u0442 \u0438\u0437\u0432\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043d\u043e, \u0442\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u044b \u0441\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u0435\u0433\u043e \u0441\u043e\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0435"}]},{id:"57",question:"\u0412 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u0435 \u0432\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u0446\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e \u0440\u0435\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438"},{answerText:"\u0436\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"}]},{id:"58",question:"\u0415\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0431\u044b \u0432\u044b \u0431\u044b\u043b\u0438 \u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043c, \u0432\u044b \u0431\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u043b\u0438 \u043f\u0440\u0435\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u0440\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044b"},{answerText:"\u0442\u0435\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0442\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044b"}]},{id:"59",question:"\u0427\u0442\u043e, \u043f\u043e-\u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435\u043c\u0443, \u0445\u0443\u0436\u0435 \u2013 \u0431\u044b\u0442\u044c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0441\u043b\u0438\u0448\u043a\u043e\u043c \u0432\u0441\u043f\u044b\u043b\u044c\u0447\u0438\u0432\u044b\u043c"},{answerText:"\u0441\u043b\u0438\u0448\u043a\u043e\u043c \u043e\u0431\u044a\u0435\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432\u043d\u044b\u043c"}]},{id:"60",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u044f \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a\u043e\u043c \u0432 \u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u043e\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0432\u043e\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u044f\u0449\u0438\u043c"},{answerText:"\u0432\u0435\u0440\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0438 \u043e\u0442\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0447\u0438\u0432\u044b\u043c"}]},{id:"61",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0441\u0438\u0442\u0443\u0430\u0446\u0438\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0443\u043f\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0434\u043e\u0447\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0438 \u0440\u0430\u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435"},{answerText:"\u043d\u0435\u0443\u043f\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0434\u043e\u0447\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u0440\u0430\u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435"}]},{id:"62",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043f\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0443\u043f\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0447\u0430\u0449\u0435 \u0432 \u0441\u043e\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0438 \u0441 \u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u0430\u043c\u0438, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u043f\u043e \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435\u0439 \u0432\u043e\u043b\u0435"},{answerText:"\u0447\u0430\u0449\u0435 \u043f\u043e \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435\u0439 \u0432\u043e\u043b\u0435, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u0432 \u0441\u043e\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0438 \u0441 \u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u0430\u043c\u0438"}]},{id:"63",question:"\u041e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0432\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a"},{answerText:"\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043a\u043e\u0439\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0438 \u0441\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439"}]},{id:"64",question:"\u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u043f\u0438\u0448\u0438\u0442\u0435, \u0432\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0431\u0443\u043a\u0432\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"},{answerText:"\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u043e"}]},{id:"65",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0442\u0440\u0443\u0434\u043d\u0435\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0435\u0431\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0445 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439"},{answerText:"\u043f\u043e\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c, \u043a\u0430\u043a \u0438\u0437\u0432\u043b\u0435\u0447\u044c \u043d\u0430\u0438\u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0443\u044e \u0432\u044b\u0433\u043e\u0434\u0443 \u0438\u0437 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0445 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439"}]},{id:"66",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043f\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043b\u0430\u043b\u0438 \u0431\u044b \u0441\u0435\u0431\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u044f\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438 \u0443\u043c\u0430"},{answerText:"\u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u043e\u0439 \u0441\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438 \u043a \u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0434\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044e"}]},{id:"67",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u043b\u0438 \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441 \u0440\u0443\u043a\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043c, \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u043b\u0438\u0432"},{answerText:"\u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0434\u043e\u0431\u0440\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d"}]},{id:"68",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0437\u0430\u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0441\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u0438\u044f"},{answerText:"\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043d\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0441\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u0438\u044f"}]},{id:"69",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0435 \u0441\u043a\u043b\u043e\u043d\u043d\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0443\u043c\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438 \u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{answerText:"\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043f\u043e \u043e\u0431\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0430\u043c"}]},{id:"70",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0448\u0430 \u0440\u0435\u0447\u044c \u0437\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0443\u044e \u043e\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0436\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438 \u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u0438, \u0432\u044b \u043d\u0435 \u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0437\u043d\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0441\u043a\u0430\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430 \u0441\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u044f \u043d\u0435 \u0443\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0448\u0438\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"71",question:"\u0423 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0448\u0438\u0440\u043e\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u043a\u0440\u0443\u0433 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0438 \u0432\u044b \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0438\u0445 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439, \u0441 \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c, \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438\u043c\u0438 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0437\u044c\u044f\u043c\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"72",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u043d\u0430\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0438 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u043e\u0433\u043e \u043a\u043e\u043b\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0430 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"73",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0435 \u043c\u0435\u0448\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u0440\u0430\u0434\u0438\u043e \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0442\u0435\u043b\u0435\u0432\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0440, \u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0441 \u043a\u0435\u043c-\u0442\u043e \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0433\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"74",question:"\u0421 \u0432\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e \u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u043e \u043f\u043e\u0437\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043c\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u043e\u0439\u0442\u0438 \u0432 \u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"75",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441 \u0443\u0434\u043e\u0432\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435\u043c \u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0447\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0430 \u0437\u0432\u043e\u043d\u044f\u0449\u0438\u0439 \u0442\u0435\u043b\u0435\u0444\u043e\u043d, \u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e, \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0443 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0435\u0441\u0442\u044c \u043a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u0435-\u0442\u043e \u043d\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438, \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e \u043f\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"76",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043d\u0430 \u0432\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0438\u043d\u043a\u0430\u0445 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0432 \u0433\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438, \u0438 \u0432\u044b \u043b\u044e\u0431\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0437\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043c\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0441 \u043d\u043e\u0432\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044c\u043c\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"77",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441 \u0433\u0440\u0443\u043f\u043f\u043e\u0439 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0432 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0434\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"78",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043e\u0447\u0435\u043d\u044c \u0431\u044b\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e \u0443\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u044b\u043d\u0443\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u044b \u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0443\u0436\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043e\u0431\u0434\u0443\u043c\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0447\u0442\u043e-\u043b\u0438\u0431\u043e \u0432 \u0442\u0435\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0434\u043b\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e \u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438, \u0431\u0435\u0437 \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438 \u043f\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0441 \u043a\u0435\u043c-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0438\u043c\u0438 \u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u044f\u043c\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"79",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0433\u043e\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0434\u043e \u0442\u0440\u0443\u0434\u043d\u0435\u0435 \u0441\u043b\u0443\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u0433\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0438\u0442\u044c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"80",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0442\u0440\u0435\u0431\u0443\u044e\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0441\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0434\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u043e\u043a\u0440\u0443\u0436\u0430\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0445 \u043e \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u043a\u0430\u043a \u0432\u044b \u0432\u044b\u0433\u043b\u044f\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435, \u0438 \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043e\u043a\u0440\u0443\u0436\u0430\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0435 \u0434\u0443\u043c\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u043e \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u043a\u0430\u043a \u0443 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0442\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"81",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u0434\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u0445\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0448\u043e \u0432\u044b\u0433\u043b\u044f\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0443 \u0432\u0430\u0441, \u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0442\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u043d\u043e \u0442\u0435\u043c \u043d\u0435 \u043c\u0435\u043d\u0435\u0435, \u0432\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432 \u044d\u0442\u043e, \u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0443\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0448\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0434\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043e\u0442 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0445",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"82",question:"\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0437\u0430\u0440\u044f\u0436\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u044d\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0433\u0438\u0435\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Extravert"},{id:"83",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u043f\u043e\u0432\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430 \u0432 \u0443\u043c\u0435, \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0434 \u0442\u0435\u043c, \u043a\u0430\u043a \u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438\u0445 \u0432 \u0441\u043b\u0443\u0445",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"84",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043d\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043a\u043e \u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0447\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0430 \u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u044b \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0445 \xab\u042f \u043f\u043e\u0434\u0443\u043c\u0430\u044e\xbb \u0438\u043b\u0438 \xab\u042f \u0441\u043a\u0430\u0436\u0443 \u043f\u043e\u0437\u0436\u0435\xbb",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"85",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043b\u044e\u0431\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0430\u0436\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0434\u0430\u0442\u044b \u0442\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e \u0441 \u0441\u0430\u043c\u044b\u043c \u0431\u043b\u0438\u0437\u043a\u0438\u043c \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a\u043e\u043c \u0438\u043b\u0438, \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e, \u0432 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u043f\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0438 \u043b\u0438\u0448\u044c \u043d\u0435\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u0438\u0445 \u0441\u0430\u043c\u044b\u0445 \u0431\u043b\u0438\u0437\u043a\u0438\u0445 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0437\u0435\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"86",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043f\u043e\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0438 \u0442\u0438\u0448\u0438\u043d\u0430",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"87",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043b\u044e\u0431\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f \u043d\u0430\u0435\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0435 \u0441 \u0441\u0430\u043c\u0438\u043c \u0441\u043e\u0431\u043e\u0439 \u0438\u043b\u0438, \u043f\u043e \u043a\u0440\u0430\u0439\u043d\u0435\u0439 \u043c\u0435\u0440\u0435, \u043d\u0435 \u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0442\u0438\u0432 \u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0433\u043e \u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f\u043f\u0440\u0435\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"88",question:"\u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u043f\u044b\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u0441\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u0447\u0435\u043c-\u0442\u043e, \u043b\u044e\u0431\u043e\u0439 \u0448\u0443\u043c, \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0439 \u0442\u0435\u043b\u0435\u0432\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0440, \u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0451\u043d\u043d\u0430\u044f \u043c\u0443\u0437\u044b\u043a\u0430 \u0438 \u0442.\u0434. \u0442\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0434\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"89",question:"\u0418\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u043d\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0441\u0442\u0435\u0441\u043d\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0437\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0447\u0438\u0432\u044b\u043c. \u0412\u044b \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0435\u0431\u044f \u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u043c, \u043d\u043e \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0430 \u0441\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u0430\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0432 \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0433\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0435 \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442 \u0442\u0440\u0430\u043a\u0442\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u043c\u0438 \u0438\u043c\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e \u0442\u0430\u043a\u0438\u043c \u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043e\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"90",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u0432\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u043c, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"91",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u044b \u0445\u043e\u0442\u0435\u043b\u0438 \u043d\u0430\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0443\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044e \u0431\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0435 \u044d\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0433\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0432\u044b\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0438 \u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0438 \u044d\u043c\u043e\u0446\u0438\u0438 \u0438 \u0447\u0430\u0449\u0435 \u0432\u044b\u0441\u0442\u0443\u043f\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0432 \u0440\u043e\u043b\u0438 \u0438\u043d\u0438\u0446\u0438\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0440\u0430 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"92",question:"\u041c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0438\u0435 \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0445\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0448\u0438\u043c \u0441\u043b\u0443\u0448\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"93",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0432\u044b\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0438 \u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0438 \u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0430 \u0438 \u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c\u044e \u0437\u0430\u043a\u0430\u043d\u0447\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438 \u0444\u0440\u0430\u0437\u044b \u0431\u0435\u0437 \u0442\u043e\u0433\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0431\u044b\u0442\u044c \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0440\u0432\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438\u043c \u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u0441\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"94",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043e\u0447\u0435\u043d\u044c, \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u043e\u0449\u0443\u0449\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0435\u043e\u0431\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043c\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u043f\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u044c \u0432 \u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u043e\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435, \u0432 \u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438 \u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435 \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0441\u0438\u0432\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0432 \u0433\u0440\u0443\u043f\u043f\u0435 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"95",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0442\u044f\u0436\u0435\u043b\u043e \u0432\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0432 \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0442 \u0441 \u043d\u0435\u0437\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043c\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044c\u043c\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Introvert"},{id:"96",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0434\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0435\u0442, \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u0434\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u043c \u0447\u0435\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0445 \u0443\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0439 \u0438 \u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0446\u0438\u0439 \u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u043e\u0431\u044a\u044f\u0441\u043d\u044f\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u043c \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u043a\u043e\u043d\u043a\u0440\u0435\u0442\u043d\u043e \u0438 \u0434\u0435\u0442\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"97",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0432 \u043d\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u0449\u0438\u0439 \u043c\u043e\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442, \u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u0437\u0430\u0434\u0443\u043c\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u043e \u0431\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0449\u0435\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"98",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0447\u0442\u043e-\u0442\u043e \u043a\u043e\u043d\u043a\u0440\u0435\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0435, \u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u0442\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e \u0434\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043e\u0431 \u044d\u0442\u043e\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"99",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430, \u0440\u0435\u0437\u0443\u043b\u044c\u0442\u0430\u0442\u043e\u043c \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0439 \u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0447\u0442\u043e-\u0442\u043e \u0440\u0435\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u0438 \u043e\u0449\u0443\u0442\u0438\u043c\u043e\u0435, \u043d\u0430\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0440, \u0442\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0440\u044b \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0443\u0441\u043b\u0443\u0433\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"100",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0435 \u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u043d\u043d\u0430 \u043f\u043e\u043d\u044f\u0442\u043d\u043e \u0441\u0442\u0440\u0435\u043c\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043d\u0435\u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0445 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439 \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f \u0441\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438 \u0443\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u043a\u0440\u0443\u0433 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"101",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043d\u0435 \u043e\u0447\u0435\u043d\u044c \u043b\u044e\u0431\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0444\u0430\u043d\u0442\u0430\u0437\u0438\u044f\u043c \u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u043b\u0438\u0448\u043a\u043e\u043c \u043e\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0440\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0442\u0435\u0445 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439, \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0435 \u0442\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044f\u0442 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435 \u0434\u0440\u0430\u0433\u043e\u0446\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u043d\u0435\u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u043c\u0435\u0447\u0442\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"102",question:"\u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u0441\u043c\u043e\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0430 \u043b\u0435\u0441, \u0432\u044b \u0432\u0438\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043e\u0442\u0434\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0434\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0432\u044c\u044f, \u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u0446\u0435\u043b\u044b\u0439 \u043b\u0435\u0441",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"103",question:"\u041d\u0430 \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u0437\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0438\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u043e \u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0438 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435\u0439 \u0441\u043e\u0431\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0439 \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u044b \u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u0431\u0435\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043a\u043e\u0438\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u043e \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u043a\u0430\u043a \u0435\u0435 \u0440\u0435\u0437\u0443\u043b\u044c\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044b \xab\u0432\u043f\u0438\u0448\u0443\u0442\u0441\u044f\xbb \u0432 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0443\u044e \u043a\u0430\u0440\u0442\u0438\u043d\u0443 \u0438 \u0432 \u0440\u0435\u0437\u0443\u043b\u044c\u0442\u0430\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u043e\u0440\u0433\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0437\u0430\u0446\u0438\u0438 \u0432 \u0446\u0435\u043b\u043e\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"104",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441 \u0444\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u0438 \u0446\u0438\u0444\u0440\u0430\u043c\u0438, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u0441 \u0438\u0434\u0435\u044f\u043c\u0438 \u0438 \u0430\u0431\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u043a\u0442\u043d\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u0442\u0435\u043e\u0440\u0438\u044f\u043c\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"105",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043a\u043e\u043d\u043a\u0440\u0435\u0442\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u044b \u043d\u0430 \u043a\u043e\u043d\u043a\u0440\u0435\u0442\u043d\u043e \u043f\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435, \u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u044b. \u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0448\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043a\u043e\u0433\u043e-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c: \xab\u041a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0439 \u0447\u0430\u0441?\xbb, \u0432\u0430\u043c \u0431\u044b \u0445\u043e\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0441\u044c \u0443\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442, \u043d\u0430\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0440, \xab3:52\xbb, \u0438 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442 \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0434\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442, \u043a\u0430\u043a \xab\u043e\u043a\u043e\u043b\u043e \u0447\u0435\u0442\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0445\xbb",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"106",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0438 \u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u0438, \u0430 \u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u043c\u0438 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044c\u043c\u0438 \u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0431\u0443\u043a\u0432\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e, \u043d\u0435 \u043f\u044b\u0442\u0430\u044f\u0441\u044c \u043d\u0430\u0439\u0442\u0438 \u0432 \u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0445 \u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u043e\u0435 \u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0441\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439 \u0441\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"107",question:"\u0415\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u044b \u0432\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432 \u0411\u043e\u0433\u0430, \u0442\u043e \u0432\u0430\u043c \u0445\u043e\u0447\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u043c-\u0442\u043e \u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043e\u043c \u043f\u0440\u043e\u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u044e \u0432\u0435\u0440\u0443 - \u043d\u0430\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0440, \u0447\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0437 \u0445\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0448\u0438\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0443\u043f\u043a\u0438, \u043c\u043e\u043b\u0438\u0442\u0432\u0443 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0440\u0435\u0433\u0443\u043b\u044f\u0440\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0441\u0435\u0449\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0446\u0435\u0440\u043a\u0432\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Sensing"},{id:"108",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043b\u044e\u0431\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043d\u0430 \u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u044b \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0438\u0435 \u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"109",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u043f\u043e\u0447\u0435\u043c\u0443 \u043c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0438\u0435 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u043c\u043e\u0433\u0443\u0442 \u0441 \u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c\u044e \u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438\u043c \u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0446\u0438\u044f\u043c, \u0438 \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0434\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c, \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u043e\u043d\u0438 \u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u044b\u043f\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438\u0437 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0434\u0435\u0442\u0430\u043b\u0438 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0441\u043b\u0438\u0448\u043a\u043e\u043c \u043c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0448\u0438\u0432\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441, \u043f\u044b\u0442\u0430\u044f\u0441\u044c \u0443\u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0432 \u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435\u0433\u043e \u043f\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"110",question:"\u0411\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0435 \u0438 \u0442\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438, \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0435 \u043e\u043d\u043e \u043a\u0440\u043e\u0435\u0442 \u0432 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u0435, \u0433\u043e\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0434\u043e \u0431\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0435 \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0433\u0443\u044e\u0442, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u043f\u0443\u0433\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"111",question:"\u0427\u0430\u0449\u0435 \u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e \u0432\u0430\u043c \u0433\u043e\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0434\u043e \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0441\u043d\u0435\u0435 \u0440\u0430\u0437\u043c\u044b\u0448\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c \u043e \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u043a\u0443\u0434\u0430 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0436\u0438\u0437\u043d\u044c \u0447\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0437 \u043d\u0435\u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0435 \u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u043e \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u0433\u0434\u0435 \u0432\u044b \u043d\u0430\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u0432 \u0436\u0438\u0437\u043d\u0438 \u0432 \u043d\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u0449\u0438\u0439 \u043c\u043e\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"112",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0443\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043d\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0435, \u0434\u0430\u0436\u0435 \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u044d\u0442\u043e \u043d\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0435 \u0437\u043d\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043d\u0435 \u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442 \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u043d\u0438\u043a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0433\u043e \u043f\u0440\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0433\u043e \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0432 \u043d\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u0449\u0435\u043c, \u0430 \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e, \u0434\u0430\u0436\u0435 \u0438 \u0432 \u0431\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0449\u0435\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"113",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0434\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043e \u043d\u0435\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u0438\u0445 \u0432\u0435\u0449\u0430\u0445 \u043e\u0434\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0437\u0430\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u043d\u0435\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u0438\u043c\u0438 \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u043e\u0434\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"114",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043e\u0447\u0435\u043d\u044c \u043d\u0435 \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430, \u0432 \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0439 \u043d\u0435\u043e\u0431\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043c\u043e \u0438\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044c \u0434\u0435\u043b\u043e \u0441 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0438\u043c \u043a\u043e\u043b\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u043c \u043c\u0435\u043b\u043a\u0438\u0445 \u0434\u0435\u0442\u0430\u043b\u0435\u0439 \u0438 \u0444\u0430\u043a\u0442\u043e\u0432",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"115",question:"\u0412\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0432\u0430\u0441 - \u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e. \u0412\u044b \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u043e\u043f\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438 \u043a\u0443\u0434\u0430-\u043b\u0438\u0431\u043e, \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0442\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e \u0432\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0447\u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u043d\u0430\u0447\u0430\u043b\u0430\u0441\u044c \u0431\u0435\u0437 \u0432\u0430\u0441",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"116",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c \u043a\u0430\u043b\u0430\u043c\u0431\u0443\u0440\u044b \u0438 \u0438\u0433\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043c\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"117",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043d\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0447\u044c \u0442\u0435\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0442\u0438\u0437\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438 \u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u043e \u0432\u043e\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0430\u0431\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u043a\u0442\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u043d\u044f\u0442\u0438\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"118",question:"\u0414\u043b\u044f \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0441\u0443\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0435\u0449\u0435\u0439, \u0432\u044b\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0435\u043d\u043d\u0430\u044f \u0432 \u0441\u0438\u043c\u0432\u043e\u043b\u0438\u043a\u0435 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0432 \u0438\u0445 \u0441\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u043e\u043c \u0441\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b\u0435, \u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u0430\u0436\u043d\u0435\u0435, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u0432\u043d\u0435\u0448\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u044f\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"119",question:"\u0415\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u044b \u0438 \u0432\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432 \u0411\u043e\u0433\u0430, \u0442\u043e \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0438\u043a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u043c \u0432\u043d\u0435\u0448\u043d\u0438\u043c \u0440\u0438\u0442\u0443\u0430\u043b\u0430\u043c. \u0412\u0430\u0448\u0430 \u0432\u0435\u0440\u0430 \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442 \u0441\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438 \u0431\u0435\u0437 \u043a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u0445-\u0442\u043e \u0432\u043d\u0435\u0448\u043d\u0438\u0445 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u044f\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0439 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0439 \u0441 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u043d\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Intuitive"},{id:"120",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0441\u043f\u043e\u043a\u043e\u0439\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0438 \u043e\u0431\u044a\u0435\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0432 \u0442\u0435\u0445 \u0441\u0438\u0442\u0443\u0430\u0446\u0438\u044f\u0445, \u0432 \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0445 \u043c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0438\u0435 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0435 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0438 \u0442\u0435\u0440\u044f\u044e\u0442 \u0441\u0430\u043c\u043e\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0430\u0434\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u044f\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0438\u0437\u043b\u0438\u0448\u043d\u0435 \u044d\u043c\u043e\u0446\u0438\u043e\u043d\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u043c\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"121",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435 \u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0443\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0447\u0435\u0439-\u0442\u043e \u0441\u043f\u043e\u0440, \u0431\u0430\u0437\u0438\u0440\u0443\u044f\u0441\u044c \u043d\u0430 \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043d\u043e \u0438 \u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u043b\u0438\u0432\u043e, \u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u043d\u0430 \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u043a\u0430\u043a \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435 \u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0432\u043b\u0438\u044f\u0435\u0442 \u043d\u0430 \u0432\u0441\u0435\u0445 \u0443\u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0432 \u0441\u043f\u043e\u0440\u0430",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"122",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043b\u044e\u0431\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0434\u043e\u043a\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u044e \u0442\u043e\u0447\u043a\u0443 \u0437\u0440\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0442\u043e\u0433\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0434\u043e\u0431\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u044f\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"123",question:"\u0418\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u044b\u0434\u0432\u0438\u0433\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0430\u0440\u0433\u0443\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442\u044b \u0432 \u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443 \u043e\u0431\u0435\u0438\u0445 \u0442\u043e\u0447\u0435\u043a \u0437\u0440\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f, \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0435 \u0434\u0438\u0441\u043a\u0443\u0442\u0438\u0440\u0443\u044e\u0442\u0441\u044f, \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0432\u043b\u0435\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0442\u043e\u0433\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u043f\u043e\u0443\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0436\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0439 \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"124",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0431\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0435 \u0436\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u043c\u044f\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"125",question:"\u0415\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u044b \u0441 \u043a\u0435\u043c-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043d\u044b, \u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0441\u043a\u0430\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0438\u043c \u043e\u0431 \u044d\u0442\u043e\u043c, \u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u043c\u043e\u043b\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0437\u0432\u043e\u043b\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0435\u043c\u0443 \u0434\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043e\u043d \u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"126",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0435 \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c, \u043f\u043e\u0447\u0435\u043c\u0443 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0438 \u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0438\u0432\u0430\u044e\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0438\u0437-\u0437\u0430 \u043a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u0445-\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0435\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0432\u0435\u0449\u0435\u0439, \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0435, \u043a\u0430\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f, \u043d\u0435 \u0438\u043c\u0435\u044e\u0442 \u043d\u0438\u043a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0433\u043e \u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u043a \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0443",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"127",question:"\u0412\u044b, \u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435 \u0431\u0443\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0434\u043e\u043a\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u044e \u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043e\u0442\u0443, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u0441\u0442\u0430\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u043f\u043e\u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044f\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"128",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0442\u043e\u0433\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0445\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0448\u043e \u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u044e \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0443, \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0435 \u043e\u0431\u044f\u0437\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e \u043d\u0430\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0432 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0436\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0445 \u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f\u0445 \u0441 \u043a\u043e\u043b\u043b\u0435\u0433\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u043f\u043e \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0435",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"129",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435 \u0443\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0431\u044b\u0442\u044c \u043e\u0431\u044a\u0435\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432\u043d\u044b\u043c, \u043d\u0435\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0442\u0440\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u0442\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0435\u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0435 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0438 \u043e\u0431\u0432\u0438\u043d\u044f\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0432 \u0445\u043b\u0430\u0434\u043d\u043e\u043a\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0438 \u0438 \u043d\u0435\u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Rational"},{id:"130",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u043e\u0431\u0432\u0438\u043d\u044f\u044e\u0442 \u0432 \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u0441\u0435 \xab\u0441\u043b\u0438\u0448\u043a\u043e\u043c \u0431\u043b\u0438\u0437\u043a\u043e \u043a \u0441\u0435\u0440\u0434\u0446\u0443\xbb \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u043e\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430 \xab\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0441\u0447\u0443\u0440 \u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e\xbb",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"131",question:"\u0412\u044b \xab\u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043b\u0435\u0437\u0442\u044c \u0438\u0437 \u043a\u043e\u0436\u0438 \u0432\u043e\u043d\xbb, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0441\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043a\u043e\u043c\u0443-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c \u043f\u0440\u0438\u044f\u0442\u043d\u043e. \u0412\u044b \u0434\u0430\u0436\u0435 \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0438 \u0432 \u0436\u0435\u0440\u0442\u0432\u0443 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0439 \u0441\u043e\u0431\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u0444\u043e\u0440\u0442, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0441\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0443\u0434\u043e\u0431\u043d\u043e \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u044f\u0442\u043d\u043e \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u043c \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044f\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"132",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0433\u0430\u0440\u043c\u043e\u043d\u0438\u044e \u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0439 \u044f\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438 \u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0443\u0434\u043a\u0430",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"133",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0441 \u0441\u043c\u0443\u0449\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0444\u043b\u0438\u043a\u0442\u044b \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0441\u0441\u043e\u0440\u044b \u043d\u0430 \u0441\u0435\u043c\u0435\u0439\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0441\u0431\u043e\u0440\u0438\u0449\u0430\u0445 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0432 \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0445 \u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0445, \u0433\u0434\u0435 \u0432\u044b \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u0443\u0442\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c. \u0412\u044b \u0441\u0442\u0430\u0440\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c \u043b\u0438\u0431\u043e \u0438\u0437\u0431\u0435\u0433\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043f\u043e\u0434\u043e\u0431\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0444\u043b\u0438\u043a\u0442\u043e\u0432, \u043b\u0438\u0431\u043e \u0441\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0436\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438\u0445",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"134",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441 \u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c\u044e \xab\u0432\u0437\u044f\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0438 \u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430 \u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u043d\u043e\xbb, \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u043f\u043e\u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043e\u043d\u0438 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u0443-\u0442\u043e \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043e\u0431\u0438\u0434\u0443",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"135",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435 \u043c\u044f\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u0447\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0435\u043a, \u0447\u0435\u043c \u0436\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"136",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u044f\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f, \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u043e \u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0430 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"137",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043f\u043e\u043c\u043e\u0433\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044f\u043c \u0438 \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043b\u044e\u0434\u044f\u043c \u043f\u0440\u0438\u044f\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0435, \u0445\u043e\u0442\u044f \u0438\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0438 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"138",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0443\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0435\u0431\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e, \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0445 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439 \u0438 \u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u044d\u0442\u043e, \u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u0435-\u0442\u043e \u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f, \u043a\u0430\u0441\u0430\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0435\u0441\u044f \u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u0438\u0445",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"139",question:"\u0415\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0432\u044b \u0438\u0441\u043f\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u0435-\u0442\u043e \u0441\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0430, \u0442\u043e \u0443 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u043d\u0430 \u0433\u043b\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0445 \u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u043e \u043c\u043e\u0433\u0443\u0442 \u0432\u044b\u0441\u0442\u0443\u043f\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0441\u043b\u0435\u0437\u044b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Feeling"},{id:"140",question:"\u0412\u044b \u0447\u0430\u0449\u0435 \u0442\u043e\u0442, \u043a\u0442\u043e \u0434\u043e\u0436\u0438\u0434\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f, \u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u0442\u043e\u0442, \u043a\u0442\u043e \u043e\u043f\u0430\u0437\u0434\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"141",question:"\u041a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u044b \u0443\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043c \u0432\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0432\u044b \u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0445\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0448\u043e \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u0435, \u043a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u043c \u0431\u0443\u0434\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0448 \u0434\u0435\u043d\u044c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"142",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0448\u0438 \u0434\u043d\u0438 \u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e \u0440\u0430\u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u044b, \u0438 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442 \u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0442\u044c, \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0447\u0442\u043e-\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0435 \u0438\u0434\u0435\u0442 \u043f\u043e \u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0443",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"143",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043e\u0447\u0435\u043d\u044c \u043b\u044e\u0431\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0434\u043e\u043a, \u0438 \u0443 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0435\u0441\u0442\u044c \u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u0430\u044f \u0441\u0438\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043c\u0430, \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0439 \u0432\u044b \u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0441\u044c, \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0442\u043e\u0433\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0440\u0435\u0433\u0443\u043b\u044f\u0440\u043d\u043e \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0432 \u043f\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0434\u043e\u043a \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438 \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430 \u0438 \u0432\u0435\u0449\u0438. \u041f\u0440\u043e\u0446\u0435\u0441\u0441 \u0443\u0431\u043e\u0440\u043a\u0438 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c \u0432 \u043f\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0434\u043e\u043a \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0432\u043d\u0443\u0442\u0440\u0435\u043d\u043d\u0435 \xab\u043e\u0447\u0438\u0449\u0430\u0435\u0442\xbb",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"144",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0437\u0430\u043a\u0430\u043d\u0447\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043d\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044b\u0435 \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430, \u0438 \u0432\u044b \u0438\u0441\u043f\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u043e\u0435 \u043d\u0430\u0441\u043b\u0430\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435, \u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0447\u0442\u043e-\u0442\u043e \u0434\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0434\u043e \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0446\u0430. \u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c \u0441\u043f\u0438\u0441\u043a\u0438 \u0434\u0435\u043b \u0438 \u043f\u043e \u043c\u0435\u0440\u0435 \u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0432\u044b\u0447\u0435\u0440\u043a\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438\u0437 \u044d\u0442\u043e\u0433\u043e \u0441\u043f\u0438\u0441\u043a\u0430 \u0442\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0443\u0436\u0435 \u0441\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u043d\u043e",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"145",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0435 \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u044f\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0441\u044e\u0440\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0437\u044b \u0438 \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u044b \u0432 \u0436\u0438\u0437\u043d\u0438",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"146",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435 \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0438 \u0437\u043d\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0442\u043e\u0433\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435\u0439 \u0436\u0438\u0437\u043d\u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043d\u0435\u043e\u0436\u0438\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"147",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f, \u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0443 \u043a\u0430\u0436\u0434\u043e\u0439 \u0432\u0435\u0449\u0438 \u0435\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435 \u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e \u0438 \u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u0440\u0430\u0437\u043b\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043d\u043e \u043f\u043e \u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Reasonable"},{id:"148",question:"\u0412\u0430\u0448\u0435 \u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u043e \u043e\u0442\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u043b\u044e\u0434\u0435\u0439 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0441\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u0438\u044f, \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u044f\u0449\u0438\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u043a\u0440\u0443\u0433 \u0432\u0430\u0441",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"149",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e \u043d\u0435 \u043f\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0440\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0434\u043e\u043a \u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0437\u0430\u0434\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0439 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0434\u0435\u043b, \u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u0442\u0443\u043f\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043a \u0438\u0445 \u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044e \u0438 \u0434\u043e \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0446\u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0434\u043b\u044f \u044d\u0442\u043e\u0433\u043e \u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u043e",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"150",question:"\u041b\u044e\u0434\u0438 \u0447\u0430\u0441\u0442\u043e \u043e\u0431\u0432\u0438\u043d\u044f\u044e\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0432 \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u043d\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u043e \u043e\u0440\u0433\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u044b, \u0445\u043e\u0442\u044f \u0432\u044b \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u044d\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0435 \u0442\u0430\u043a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"151",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0430\u043a\u043a\u0443\u0440\u0430\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u0434\u0430 \u0438 \u0432\u043e \u0432\u0441\u0435\u043c - \u043e\u0431\u044f\u0437\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u0430. \u0418 \u0445\u043e\u0442\u044f \u0432\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043f\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0434\u043e\u043a, \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0432\u0430\u0436\u043d\u0435\u0435 \u0432\u0430\u0448 \u0442\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u043d\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0439, \u0441\u043f\u043e\u043d\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0438 \u0436\u0435\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043d\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c \u043d\u0438 \u043e\u0434\u043d\u043e\u0439 \u0438\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0439 \u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438, \u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u0443\u044e \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442 \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0430\u043c \u0441\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"152",question:"\u0412\u044b \u043e\u0431\u044b\u0447\u043d\u043e \u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u0430\u0434\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430 \u0434\u043e \u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0435\u0433\u043e, \u0438 \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0443\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0438\u0445 \u0432 \u0441\u0440\u043e\u043a, \u0442\u043e \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u044d\u0442\u043e \u0431\u043b\u0430\u0433\u043e\u0434\u0430\u0440\u044f \u043e\u0433\u0440\u043e\u043c\u043d\u044b\u043c \u0443\u0441\u0438\u043b\u0438\u044f\u043c \u0432 \xab\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u044e\u044e \u043c\u0438\u043d\u0443\u0442\u0443\xbb",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"153",question:"\u0412\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0441\u044f \u044d\u043a\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u043d\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0435 - \u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c \u044d\u0442\u043e \u043d\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0435 \u0431\u043b\u044e\u0434\u043e \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043d\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439 \u043c\u0430\u0440\u0448\u0440\u0443\u0442 \u0441 \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u044b \u0434\u043e\u043c\u043e\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Spontaneous"},{id:"154",question:"\u0414\u043b\u044f \u0442\u043e\u0433\u043e, \u0447\u0442\u043e\u0431\u044b \u0434\u043e\u0431\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f \u0443\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0445\u0430 \u0432 \u0442\u043e\u043c, \u0447\u0442\u043e \u0432\u044b \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u043d\u0430\u0448\u0430 \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430 \u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u043d\u0430 \u0443\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0438 \xab\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0430\u0442\u044c\xbb \u0432\u0430\u0441. \u0412\u044b \u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435, \u0447\u0442\u043e, \u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438 \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0432\u0430\u0441 \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0432\u043b\u0435\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435\u043c, \u043e\u043d\u0430, \u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435 \u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e, \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u0438\u0442 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438\u0445 \u0443\u0441\u0438\u043b\u0438\u0439",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0434\u0430"},{answerText:"\u041d\u0435\u0442"}],category:"Spontaneous"}],y=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(c.a)(n);function n(){return Object(i.a)(this,n),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:this.props.buttonList&&"list-bg-container-resp",onClick:this.props.closeModal}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:this.props.buttonList?"list-container-resp":"list-container",id:"modal",children:Object(d.jsx)("ul",{children:this.props.listItem})})]})}}]),n}(o.a.Component),T=n(109),m=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(c.a)(n);function n(e){var s;return Object(i.a)(this,n),(s=t.call(this,e)).state={email:"",sentEmail:!1,time:0,spinner:!1},s.formatTime=function(e){var t=Math.floor(e/60),n=e%60;return(t<10?"0"+t:t)+":"+(n<10?"0"+n:n)},s.handleChange=function(e){s.setState({email:e.target.value})},s.exportPDFWithComponent=function(){s.pdfExportComponent.current&&s.pdfExportComponent.current.save()},s.componentDidMount=function(){s.myInterval=setInterval((function(){s.setState((function(e){return{time:e.time+1}}))}),1e3),document.getElementById("1__span").style.display="none"},s.pdfExportComponent=o.a.createRef(),s}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"componentWillUnmount",value:function(){clearInterval(this.myInterval)}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this,t=Math.round((this.props.currentQuestion+1)/this.props.questions.length*100);return Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[this.props.spinner&&Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"wrapper",children:Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"loading-spinner"})}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{maxWidth:"100%"},children:Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"h-full full-display-flex",children:Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"".concat(this.props.showResult?"relative box box-table max-w-full":"relative box max-w-full"),style:{width:"700px"},children:[Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:this.props.showResult?Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:Object(d.jsxs)("div",{id:"myTable",children:[Object(d.jsxs)("table",{children:[Object(d.jsxs)("tr",{children:[Object(d.jsx)("th",{className:"table__column",children:"English"===this.props.language?"1 column":"1 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0431\u0438\u043a"}),Object(d.jsx)("th",{className:"table__column",children:"English"===this.props.language?"2 column":"2 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0431\u0438\u043a"}),Object(d.jsx)("th",{className:"table__column",children:"English"===this.props.language?"3 column":"3 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0431\u0438\u043a"}),Object(d.jsx)("th",{className:"table__column",children:"English"===this.props.language?"4 column":"4 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0431\u0438\u043a"}),Object(d.jsx)("th",{className:"table__column",children:"English"===this.props.language?"5 column":"5 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0431\u0438\u043a"}),Object(d.jsx)("th",{className:"table__column",children:"English"===this.props.language?"6 column":"6 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0431\u0438\u043a"}),Object(d.jsx)("th",{className:"table__column",children:"English"===this.props.language?"7 column":"7 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0431\u0438\u043a"}),Object(d.jsx)("th",{className:"table__column",children:"English"===this.props.language?"8 column":"8 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0431\u0438\u043a"}),Object(d.jsx)("th",{className:"table__column",children:"English"===this.props.language?"9 column":"9 \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0431\u0438\u043a"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("tr",{children:[Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose without__border",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"a":"\u0430"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"b":"\u0431"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose without__border",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"a":"\u0430"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"b":"\u0431"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose without__border",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"a":"\u0430"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"b":"\u0431"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose without__border",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"a":"\u0430"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"b":"\u0431"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose without__border",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"a":"\u0430"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"b":"\u0431"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose without__border",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"a":"\u0430"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"b":"\u0431"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose without__border",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"a":"\u0430"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"b":"\u0431"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose without__border",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"a":"\u0430"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"b":"\u0431"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose without__border",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"a":"\u0430"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__choose",children:"English"===this.props.language?"b":"\u0431"})]})]}),this.props.result.slice("English"===this.props.language?69:66).map((function(t,n){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:n+1===1?Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:Object(d.jsx)("tr",{children:e.props.result.slice("English"===e.props.language?69:66).slice(n,n+9).map((function(e,t){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row without__border__row",children:t+1}),"Yes"===e.value||"\u0434\u0430"===e.value?Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row",children:"\u2713"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row",children:"\xa0\xa0"})]}):Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row",children:"\u2713"})]})]})})}))})}):Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:(n+1)%9===0&&Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("tr",{}),Object(d.jsx)("tr",{children:e.props.result.slice("English"===e.props.language?69:66).slice(n,n+9).map((function(e,t){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:Object(d.jsxs)("th",{style:{border:"1px solid gray"},children:[t+1*n===8||t+1*n===9?Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row without__border__row",children:t+1*n}):Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row without__border__row font__small",style:{width:"22px"},children:t+1*n}),"Yes"===e.value||"\u0434\u0430"===e.value?Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row",children:"\u2713"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row",children:"\xa0\xa0"})]}):Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row",children:"\xa0\xa0"}),Object(d.jsx)("td",{className:"table__row",children:"\u2713"})]})]})})}))})]})})})}))]}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{display:"flex",alignItems:"center",justifyContent:"center",marginTop:"20px"},children:Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",alignItems:"center",gap:"30px",flexWrap:"wrap"},children:[Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",flexDirection:"column"},children:[Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",alignItems:"center",justifyContent:"center"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{borderRight:"1px solid black",borderBottom:"1px solid black",padding:"10px"},children:this.props.points[0].extravert}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{borderBottom:"1px solid black",padding:"10px"},children:this.props.points[0].introvert})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{padding:"10px"},children:"E"}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{padding:"10px"},children:"I"})]})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",flexDirection:"column"},children:[Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",alignItems:"center",justifyContent:"center"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{borderRight:"1px solid black",borderBottom:"1px solid black",padding:"10px"},children:this.props.points[0].sensing}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{borderBottom:"1px solid black",padding:"10px"},children:this.props.points[0].intuitive})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{padding:"10px"},children:"S"}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{padding:"10px"},children:"N"})]})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",flexDirection:"column"},children:[Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",alignItems:"center",justifyContent:"center"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{borderRight:"1px solid black",borderBottom:"1px solid black",padding:"10px"},children:this.props.points[0].rational}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{borderBottom:"1px solid black",padding:"10px"},children:this.props.points[0].feeling})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{padding:"10px"},children:"T"}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{padding:"10px"},children:"F"})]})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",flexDirection:"column"},children:[Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",alignItems:"center",justifyContent:"center"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{borderRight:"1px solid black",borderBottom:"1px solid black",padding:"10px"},children:this.props.points[0].reasonable}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{borderBottom:"1px solid black",padding:"10px"},children:this.props.points[0].spontaneous})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{padding:"10px"},children:"J"}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{padding:"10px"},children:"P"})]})]})]})})]})}):Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"box-content max-w-full",children:[Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{marginBottom:"1rem"}}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{position:"absolute",right:"40px",top:"20px"},children:Object(d.jsx)("p",{children:this.formatTime(this.state.time)})}),Object(d.jsx)(T.a,{percent:t,status:"active"}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{"aria-label":"Question Length",className:"mt-3",children:Object(d.jsx)("span",{className:"questionLength-span",children:"".concat("English"===this.props.language?"Question":"\u0412\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441"," ").concat(this.props.currentQuestion+1,"/").concat(this.props.questions.length)})}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{"aria-label":"Question",className:"mt-3 question-container",children:Object(d.jsx)("span",{className:"question-span",children:this.props.questions[this.props.currentQuestion].question})}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{role:"button",className:"mt-6 questionContainer-button",style:{maxWidth:"100%"},children:this.props.showButtons&&Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:this.props.questions[this.props.currentQuestion].answerOptions.map((function(t,n){return Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("button",{type:"submit",className:"question-button button-primary",id:n,style:{minHeight:"70px"},onClick:function(){return e.props.nextQuestion(t.answerText)},children:t.answerText}),Object(d.jsx)("span",{id:"".concat(n,"__span"),children:"English"===e.props.language?"Or":"\u0438\u043b\u0438"})]})}))})})]})})}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"footer__buttons",children:!0!==this.props.showResult?Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.props.currentQuestion>0&&this.props.backHandle,disabled:this.props.currentQuestion<=0,style:{backgroundColor:"#42b72a",color:"white",border:"none",outline:"none",height:"50px",borderRadius:"8px",cursor:"pointer",width:"120px",fontSize:"18px"},children:"<"}),Object(d.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.props.clickSubmit,style:{backgroundColor:"#0d6efd",color:"white",border:"none",outline:"none",height:"50px",borderRadius:"8px",cursor:"pointer",width:"120px"},disabled:this.props.history.length<=this.props.questions.length-2,children:"English"===this.props.language?"Show Result":"\u041f\u043e\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0440\u0435\u0437\u0443\u043b\u044c\u0442\u0430\u0442"}),Object(d.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.props.nextHandleQuestion,disabled:this.props.history.length>=this.props.questions.length-1,style:{backgroundColor:"#42b72a",color:"white",border:"none",outline:"none",height:"50px",borderRadius:"8px",cursor:"pointer",width:"120px",fontSize:"18px"},children:">"})]}):Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:Object(d.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.props.sentGmailFunction,style:{backgroundColor:"#0d6efd",color:"white",border:"none",outline:"none",height:"50px",borderRadius:"8px",cursor:"pointer",width:"120px"},children:"English"===this.props.language?"Submit":"\u041e\u0442\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c \u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442"})})})]})})})]})}}]),n}(o.a.Component),b=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(c.a)(n);function n(){return Object(i.a)(this,n),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)(y,{questions:this.props.questions,history:this.props.history,currentQuestion:this.props.currentQuestion,listItem:this.props.listItem,buttonList:this.props.buttonList,closeModal:this.props.closeModal}),Object(d.jsx)(m,{showResult:this.props.showResult,currentQuestion:this.props.currentQuestion,questions:this.props.questions,showButtons:this.props.showButtons,clickSubmit:this.props.clickSubmit,nextQuestion:this.props.nextQuestion,backHandle:this.props.backHandle,returnQuestions:this.props.returnQuestions,result:this.props.result,language:this.props.language,nextHandleQuestion:this.props.nextHandleQuestion,points:this.props.points,history:this.props.history,email:this.props.email,sentGmailFunction:this.props.sentGmailFunction,spinner:this.props.spinner})]})}}]),n}(o.a.Component),O=n(5),f=n.n(O),j=n(58),q=n.n(j),v=n(36),Y=n.n(v),k=n(37),N=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(c.a)(n);function n(){var e;Object(i.a)(this,n);for(var s=arguments.length,o=new Array(s),a=0;a<s;a++)o[a]=arguments[a];return(e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(o))).state={currentQuestion:0,showResult:!1,history:[],showButtons:!0,questions:[],buttonList:!1,showHero:!1,lastResult:[],extravertCount:0,introvertCount:0,sensingCount:0,intuitiveCount:0,rationalCount:0,feelingCount:0,reasonableCount:0,spontaneousCount:0,points:[],spinner:!1,name:"",surname:"",age:""},e.nextQuestion=function(t){var n;e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category&&("English"===e.props.language?"Extravert"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"Yes"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{extravertCount:e.extravertCount+1}})):"Introvert"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"Yes"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{introvertCount:e.introvertCount+1}})):"Sensing"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"Yes"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{sensingCount:e.sensingCount+1}})):"Intuitive"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"Yes"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{intuitiveCount:e.intuitiveCount+1}})):"Rational"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"Yes"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{rationalCount:e.rationalCount+1}})):"Feeling"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"Yes"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{feelingCount:e.feelingCount+1}})):"Reasonable"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"Yes"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{reasonableCount:e.reasonableCount+1}})):"Spontaneous"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category&&"Yes"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{spontaneousCount:e.spontaneousCount+1}})):"Extravert"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"\u0434\u0430"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{extravertCount:e.extravertCount+1}})):"Introvert"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"\u0434\u0430"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{introvertCount:e.introvertCount+1}})):"Sensing"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"\u0434\u0430"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{sensingCount:e.sensingCount+1}})):"Intuitive"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"\u0434\u0430"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{intuitiveCount:e.intuitiveCount+1}})):"Rational"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"\u0434\u0430"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{rationalCount:e.rationalCount+1}})):"Feeling"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"\u0434\u0430"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{feelingCount:e.feelingCount+1}})):"Reasonable"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category?"\u0434\u0430"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{reasonableCount:e.reasonableCount+1}})):"Spontaneous"===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].category&&"\u0434\u0430"===t&&e.setState((function(e){return{spontaneousCount:e.spontaneousCount+1}})));var s=!1;e.state.lastResult.length>0?e.state.lastResult.map((function(o,a){if(o.question===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question){var r=e.state.lastResult.findIndex((function(t){return t.question===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question}));r>-1&&(e.state.lastResult.splice(r,1),e.state.lastResult.push({id:e.state.currentQuestion,question:e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question,value:t}),n=e.state.currentQuestion+1),s=!0}return null})):(e.state.lastResult.push({id:e.state.currentQuestion,question:e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question,value:t}),n=e.state.currentQuestion+1,s=!0),s||(e.state.lastResult.push({id:e.state.currentQuestion,question:e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question,value:t}),n=e.state.currentQuestion+1),n<e.state.questions.length?e.setState((function(e){return{currentQuestion:e.currentQuestion=n}})):e.setState({currentQuestion:e.state.currentQuestion}),e.state.history.push(e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].id),e.state.questions.map((function(t){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:e.state.history.map((function(e){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:t.id===e&&Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[document.getElementById("".concat(t.id)).style.backgroundColor="green",document.getElementById("".concat(t.id)).style.color="white"]})})}))})})),e.state.questions.map((function(t){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:"green"!==document.getElementById("".concat(t.id)).style.backgroundColor&&Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:"gray"!==document.getElementById("".concat(t.id)).style.backgroundColor&&Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:t.id===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].id&&Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{})})})})}))},e.renderListItem=function(){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:e.state.questions.map((function(t){return Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:["70"===t.id&&Object(d.jsx)("hr",{style:{marginTop:"5px",height:"25px",backgroundColor:"gray"}}),Object(d.jsx)("li",{onClick:function(){e.setState((function(e){return{currentQuestion:e.currentQuestion=+ +t.id}})),e.state.questions.map((function(e){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:e.id<+t.id&&Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[document.getElementById("".concat(e.id)).style.backgroundColor="gray",document.getElementById("".concat(e.id)).style.color="white"]})})})),e.state.history.map((function(e){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:document.getElementById("".concat(+e)).style.backgroundColor="green"})})),e.setState((function(e){return{buttonList:e.buttonList=!1}}))},id:t.id,className:e.state.item&&"act-show",children:t.question})]})}))})},e.handleChange=function(t){e.setState({email:t.target.value})},e.handleChangeName=function(t){e.setState({name:t.target.value})},e.handleChangeSurname=function(t){e.setState({surname:t.target.value})},e.handleChangeAge=function(t){e.setState({age:t.target.value})},e.prevQuestion=function(){var t=e.state.currentQuestion-1;e.setState((function(e){return{currentQuestion:e.currentQuestion=t}}))},e.componentWillMount=function(){document.addEventListener("keydown",(function(t){var n=t.keyCode;37===n?e.state.currentQuestion>0&&e.prevQuestion():39===n&&e.nextQuestion()}))},e.rendeHero=function(){var t=Object(p.a)(new Set(e.state.history));return e.state.showHero?Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[Object(d.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"resp-button",onClick:function(){e.setState((function(t){return{buttonList:t.buttonList=!e.state.buttonList}}))},children:!0!==e.state.buttonList?Object(d.jsx)("svg",{width:"24",height:"24",fill:"none",children:Object(d.jsx)("path",{d:"M4 8h16M4 16h16",stroke:"currentColor","stroke-width":"2","stroke-linecap":"round","stroke-linejoin":"round"})}):Object(d.jsx)("svg",{width:"24",height:"24",fill:"none",class:"absolute top-1/2 left-1/2 -mt-3 -ml-3 transition duration-300 transform",children:Object(d.jsx)("path",{d:"M6 18L18 6M6 6l12 12",stroke:"currentColor","stroke-width":"2","stroke-linecap":"round","stroke-linejoin":"round"})})}),Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"flex container",children:Object(d.jsx)(b,{showResult:e.state.showResult,currentQuestion:e.state.currentQuestion,questions:e.state.questions,showButtons:e.state.showButtons,nextQuestion:e.nextQuestion,spinner:e.state.spinner,email:e.state.email,history:t,listItem:e.renderListItem(),backHandle:function(){return e.prevQuestion()},returnQuestions:function(){e.setState((function(e){return{showResult:e.showResult=!1}}))},result:e.state.lastResult,buttonList:e.state.buttonList,nextHandleQuestion:function(){var t=e.state.currentQuestion+1;if(console.log(e.state.currentQuestion),console.log(e.state.questions.length),e.state.currentQuestion+1<e.state.questions.length){e.setState((function(e){return{currentQuestion:e.currentQuestion=t}}));var n=!1;e.state.lastResult.length>0?e.state.lastResult.map((function(s,o){if(s.question===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question){var a=e.state.lastResult.findIndex((function(t){return t.question===e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question}));a>-1&&(e.state.lastResult.splice(a,1),e.state.lastResult.push({id:e.state.currentQuestion,question:e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question,value:""}),e.setState((function(e){return{currentQuestion:e.currentQuestion=t}}))),n=!0}return null})):(e.state.lastResult.push({id:e.state.currentQuestion,question:e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question,value:""}),e.setState((function(e){return{currentQuestion:e.currentQuestion=t}})),n=!0),n||(e.state.lastResult.push({id:e.state.currentQuestion,question:e.state.questions[e.state.currentQuestion].question,value:""}),e.setState((function(e){return{currentQuestion:e.currentQuestion=t}})))}},closeModal:function(){e.setState((function(t){return{buttonList:t.buttonList=!e.state.buttonList}}))},sentGmailFunction:function(){e.setState((function(e){return{spinner:e.spinner=!0}})),q()(document.getElementById("myTable")).then((function(t){var n=t.toDataURL("image/png");Y.a.post("".concat(k.host,"/auth/insertUsers"),{img:n,points:e.state.points,email:e.state.email,language:e.props.language}).then((function(t){e.setState((function(e){return{spinner:e.spinner=!1}})),"English"===e.props.language?f.a.fire("Good job!","You Finished Quiz","success").then((function(){window.location.reload()})):f.a.fire("\u041e\u0442\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u0430\u044f \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430!","\u0412\u0430\u0448 \u0440\u0435\u0437\u0443\u043b\u044c\u0442\u0430\u0442 \u043e\u0442\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d \u043d\u0430 \u043f\u043e\u0447\u0442\u0443. \u0421 \u0412\u0430\u043c\u0438 \u0441\u0432\u044f\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043d\u0430\u0448 \u0441\u043f\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0441\u0442","success").then((function(){window.location.reload()}))}))}))},language:e.props.language,points:e.state.points,clickSubmit:function(){e.state.history.length>=e.state.questions.length-1&&(e.state.points.push({extravert:e.state.extravertCount,introvert:e.state.introvertCount,sensing:e.state.sensingCount,intuitive:e.state.intuitiveCount,rational:e.state.rationalCount,feeling:e.state.feelingCount,reasonable:e.state.reasonableCount,spontaneous:e.state.spontaneousCount}),e.setState((function(e){return{showResult:e.showResult=!0}})),Y.a.post("".concat(k.host,"/auth/insertUser"),{img:"",points:e.state.points,email:e.state.email,result:e.state.lastResult,language:e.props.language}))}})})]})}):Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:Object(d.jsx)("form",{onSubmit:function(e){return e.preventDefault()},children:Object(d.jsx)("div",{style:{maxWidth:"100%"},children:Object(d.jsx)("div",{className:"h-full full-display-flex",children:Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"relative box max-w-full",style:{width:"500px",height:"600px",justifyContent:"center"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("h1",{style:{textAlign:"center"},children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"Input your information":"\u0412\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0443 \u0438\u043d\u0444\u043e\u0440\u043c\u0430\u0446\u0438\u044e"}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"text-center form-ai mt-3",style:{width:"100%"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",placeholder:" ",className:"input form-ai-control w-350 max-w-full",autoFocus:!0,value:e.state.name,onChange:e.handleChangeName,style:{width:"100%"}}),Object(d.jsx)("label",{children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"First name":"\u0418\u043c\u044f"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"text-center form-ai mt-3",style:{width:"100%"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",placeholder:" ",className:"input form-ai-control w-350 max-w-full",value:e.state.surname,onChange:e.handleChangeSurname,style:{width:"100%"}}),Object(d.jsx)("label",{children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"Last name":"\u0424\u0430\u043c\u0438\u043b\u0438\u044f"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"text-center form-ai mt-3",style:{width:"100%"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",placeholder:" ",className:"input form-ai-control w-350 max-w-full",value:e.state.age,onChange:e.handleChangeAge,style:{width:"100%"}}),Object(d.jsx)("label",{children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"Age":"\u0412\u043e\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("div",{className:"text-center form-ai mt-3",style:{width:"100%"},children:[Object(d.jsx)("input",{type:"text",placeholder:" ",className:"input form-ai-control w-350 max-w-full",value:e.state.email,onChange:e.handleChange,style:{width:"100%"}}),Object(d.jsx)("label",{children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"Email":"\u044d\u043b.\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0442\u0430"})]}),Object(d.jsxs)("select",{style:{border:"1px solid lightgray",outline:"none",borderRadius:"5px",marginTop:"15px",width:"100%",height:"50px",paddingLeft:"10px"},value:e.props.language,onChange:e.props.onChangeLanguage,children:[Object(d.jsx)("option",{children:"\u0420\u0443\u0441\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0439"}),Object(d.jsx)("option",{children:"English"})]}),Object(d.jsx)("button",{type:"submit",style:{backgroundColor:"#0d6efd",color:"white",fontSize:"1rem",borderRadius:"0.25rem",border:"none",outline:"none",height:"44px",marginTop:"15px",width:"100%",cursor:"pointer"},onClick:function(){e.state.name?e.state.surname?e.state.age?e.state.email?e.state.email.length<0?"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"Please enter a good email format"}):f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"\u041f\u043e\u0436\u0430\u043b\u0443\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0430, \u0432\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0444\u043e\u0440\u043c\u0430\u0442 \u044d\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0439 \u043f\u043e\u0447\u0442\u044b"}):"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"Please choose language"}):f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"\u041f\u043e\u0436\u0430\u043b\u0443\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0430, \u0432\u044b\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u044f\u0437\u044b\u043a"}):"English"===e.props.language?(e.setState((function(e){return{questions:e.questions=x}})),e.setState((function(e){return{showHero:e.showHero=!0}}))):"\u0420\u043e\u0441\u0441\u0438\u044f"===e.props.language&&(e.setState((function(e){return{questions:e.questions=g}})),e.setState((function(e){return{showHero:e.showHero=!0}}))):"English"===e.props.language?f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"Please enter a your email"}):f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"\u041f\u043e\u0436\u0430\u043b\u0443\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0430, \u0432\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u0430\u0448 \u0430\u0434\u0440\u0435\u0441 \u044d\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0439 \u043f\u043e\u0447\u0442\u044b"}):"English"===e.props.language?f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"Please enter a your age"}):f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"\u041f\u043e\u0436\u0430\u043b\u0443\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0430, \u0432\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u0430\u0448 \u0432\u043e\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442"}):"English"===e.props.language?f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"Please enter a your last name"}):f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"\u041f\u043e\u0436\u0430\u043b\u0443\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0430, \u0432\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0443 \u0444\u0430\u043c\u0438\u043b\u0438\u044e"}):"English"===e.props.language?f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"Please enter a your first name"}):f.a.fire({icon:"error",title:"Oops...",text:"\u041f\u043e\u0436\u0430\u043b\u0443\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0430, \u0432\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0435 \u0438\u043c\u044f"})},children:"English"===e.props.language||"Choose Language"===e.props.language?"Continue":"\u041f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"})]})})})})})},e}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(d.jsx)(d.Fragment,{children:this.rendeHero()})}}]),n}(o.a.Component),_=Object(h.e)(N),C=n(33),S=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(c.a)(n);function n(){var e;Object(i.a)(this,n);for(var s=arguments.length,o=new Array(s),a=0;a<s;a++)o[a]=arguments[a];return(e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(o))).state={showPopup:!1,language:"\u0420\u043e\u0441\u0441\u0438\u044f"},e.componentWillMount=function(){setTimeout((function(){e.setState((function(e){return{showPopup:e.showPopup=!0}}))}),2e3)},e}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return Object(d.jsxs)(d.Fragment,{children:[this.state.showPopup&&Object(d.jsx)(w,{language:this.state.language}),Object(d.jsx)(C.a,{children:Object(d.jsx)(h.a,{path:"/",exact:!0,children:Object(d.jsx)(_,{language:this.state.language,onChangeLanguage:function(t){return e.setState({language:t.target.value})}})})})]})}}]),n}(s.Component),I=(n(104),function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&n.e(3).then(n.bind(null,110)).then((function(t){var n=t.getCLS,s=t.getFID,o=t.getFCP,a=t.getLCP,r=t.getTTFB;n(e),s(e),o(e),a(e),r(e)}))});n(105);r.a.render(Object(d.jsx)(o.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(d.jsx)(S,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),I()},37:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"host":"https://quiz-app-second.herokuapp.com"}')},67:function(e,t,n){}},[[106,1,2]]]);